var questions = [
  {
    question: "What is the name of my school?",
    options: ["Saraswati Vidyalaya", "Saraswati Vidya Mandir", "Saraswati Vidyapeeth"],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "What do i like more?",
    options: ["Shopping", "Exercising", "Eating Junk"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Which is my favourite rom-com book?",
    options: ["Maybe Someday", "November 9", "Shadow Hunters"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Do i have a permanent license yet? ",
    options: ["Yes", "No"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What is my sibling's name?",
    options: ["Raj", "Rajesh", "Rajat"],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "What is my favorite food?",
    options: ["Anything home cooked", "Pani Puri", "Pizza"],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "What is the color of my bicycle?",
    options: ["Red", "Purple", "Pink"],
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "What do i have?",
    options: ["Earphones", "Headphones", "Both", "None"],
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Which beverage would i prefer among these?",
    options: ["Cold Coffee", "Tea", "Orange Juice"],
    answer: 0
  },
  {
    question: "Who's songs i listen to the most?",
    options: ["Ariana Grande", "Ed Sheeren", "Taylor Swift"],
    answer: 2
  },
];

var highScore = [
  {
    name: "Shraddha",
    score: 10
  },
  {
    name: "Urmila",
    score: 7
  }
]

module.exports = { questions, highScore }